<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Health on Charles M. Knox</title>
    <link>https://charlesmknox.com/categories/health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Health on Charles M. Knox</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 18:05:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://charlesmknox.com/categories/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learning How to Learn</title>
      <link>https://charlesmknox.com/health/general/learning-how-to-learn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 18:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlesmknox.com/health/general/learning-how-to-learn/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been taking the time regularly in my life to prioritize learning. I&amp;rsquo;ve been on the lookout for new things to learn.
So, I explored options for online learning. I found Coursera. A few of the top recommended online classes included a particularly interesting class called Learning How to Learn.
In this class, you really do learn how to properly learn and engage with new and confusing content. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at some of the most profound things I learned from the class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Napping: The Right Way</title>
      <link>https://charlesmknox.com/health/general/napping-the-right-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 18:05:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlesmknox.com/health/general/napping-the-right-way/</guid>
      <description>Recently I stumbled upon a Reddit post in the ChangeMyView subreddit that suggested that it should be &amp;ldquo;the standard&amp;rdquo; for employers to allow 20-minute naps around noon.
As someone that values having some downtime around lunch to close my eyes and nap, this topic was worth reviewing in detail. What are the benefits of taking naps? How long should naps actually be? When should they be taken? Can an employer allow an employee to take naps?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Sleep Matters Now More Than Ever</title>
      <link>https://charlesmknox.com/health/general/why-sleep-matters-now-more-than-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 14:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlesmknox.com/health/general/why-sleep-matters-now-more-than-ever/</guid>
      <description>The following are my notes from the TED Talks Daily podcast, Why sleep matters now more than ever | Matt Walker.
Matt Walker has an impressive set of credentials related to sleep science. View his website at sleepdiplomat.com.
Notes on Sleep, the Immune System, and COVID-19 Individuals that reported getting less than 7 hours of sleep reported a 3-fold increase of getting the Rhinovirus.
The body requires sleep in order to produce a proper immune response to even vaccines.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
