<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio on Charles M. Knox</title>
    <link>https://charlesmknox.com/categories/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio on Charles M. Knox</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://charlesmknox.com/categories/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Space Codes</title>
      <link>https://charlesmknox.com/apps/space-codes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlesmknox.com/apps/space-codes/</guid>
      <description>Space Codes is an app that plays custom, curated focus music to help you focus. It&amp;rsquo;s a simple app that has a few hours of songs I wrote myself, specifically to help people tune out the noise of every day life and fill their minds with simple, moving sounds.
👨‍🚀 About me I am an app developer and electronic musician. You can listen to my music by visiting aperspection.com, and you can see my apps here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Septaday</title>
      <link>https://charlesmknox.com/apps/septaday/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlesmknox.com/apps/septaday/</guid>
      <description>Septaday is an app that helps you live a healthier, more successful life by providing you with 7 static, daily tasks. If you reached this page via the links in the app, you can scroll around on this page to read about why each task is worth doing, with scientific research to back up each claim.
View it on the App Store here.
About me To try and provide some credibility to myself&amp;hellip; I am an Ironman triathlete, professional software and app developer, electronic musician, and some other things - but most importantly, I try to live a balanced life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BananAppeal.co: Small Business Landing Page</title>
      <link>https://charlesmknox.com/portfolio/fullstack/bananappealco/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlesmknox.com/portfolio/fullstack/bananappealco/</guid>
      <description>A booming, Etsy-based online retailer called BananAppeal.co was in need of a landing page, and I wanted to help them out. So, in less than one day, I assembled a simple (but very sleek) landing page for their business.
You can view the page here: bananappeal.co
Video Sorry, your browser doesn&#39;t support embedded videos.  Performance/Accessibility/Best Practices/SEO Using Lighthouse, the website meets almost 100% across every web-based metric:
The only metric it falls behind on is the recommendation to serve next-gen images instead of the more universally compatible jpg/png images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firefox Browser Addon Web Extension: Containers Helper</title>
      <link>https://charlesmknox.com/portfolio/webextensions/ffcontainershelper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlesmknox.com/portfolio/webextensions/ffcontainershelper/</guid>
      <description>Check out the extension View the extension here! You can also view the source code here on GitHub.
The rest of this article is a writeup on the extension itself - enjoy!
Preface Before talking about my addon directly, first I wanted to explain the context behind why it was created in the first place.
As a privacy enthusiast, I often find myself configuring my browser to match my needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Blog Site</title>
      <link>https://charlesmknox.com/portfolio/fullstack/blog-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 15:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://charlesmknox.com/portfolio/fullstack/blog-site/</guid>
      <description>Before switching to Hugo, I wrote my own full-stack website, and hosted it on AWS. The site was written in:
 Frontend: Angular 9 Middleware/web server: Go 1.13 Data: Static markdown files  Screenshots Because the website is not statically generated and requires a live API, and I do not want to continue to provide uptime for the API, I&amp;rsquo;ll be providing a few screen captures of the site in action.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
